'use strict'

const DATA = [
    {                   
        question: "Game Of Thrones is based on a series of novels which name is: ",
        optionA: "Game Of Thrones",
        optionB: "A Song Of Ice and Fire",
        optionC: "Wars of the Roses",
        optionD: "Of Mens and Dragons",
        optionE: "The Accursed Kings",
        correctAnswer: "A Song Of Ice and Fire"
    },
    {                   
        question: "The phrase &quotThat's what I do, I drink and I know things&quot it's credited to: ",
        optionA: "Cercei Lannister",
        optionB: "Tywin Lannister",
        optionC: "Tyrion Lannister",
        optionD: "Robert Baratheon",
        optionE: "Oberyn Martell",
        correctAnswer: "Tyrion Lannister"
    },
    {                   
        question: "By the end of Season Seven how many direwolves are still alive: ",
        optionA: "Two",
        optionB: "Three",
        optionC: "Four",
        optionD: "Five",
        optionE: "Six",
        correctAnswer: "Two"
    },
    {                   
        question: "Which TV chain holds the copyright of GoT: ",
        optionA: "FOX",
        optionB: "AMC",
        optionC: "HBO",
        optionD: "SHOWTIME",
        optionE: "TNT",
        correctAnswer: "HBO"
    },
    {                   
        question: "How many children Eddard &quotNed&quot Stark had: " ,
        optionA: "Three",
        optionB: "Four",
        optionC: "Four and a half",
        optionD: "Five",
        optionE: "Six",        
        correctAnswer: "Five"
    },
    {                   
        question: "GoT is the most Emmy award winning TV show in the history of Television with:  ",
        optionA: "12 Emmys",
        optionB: "38 Emmys",
        optionC: "24 Emmys",
        optionD: "42 Emmys",
        optionE: "51 Emmys",
        correctAnswer: "38 Emmys"
    },
    {                   
        question: "Who composed GoT Main Theme song: ",
        optionA: "Hans Zimmer",
        optionB: "Vangelis",
        optionC: "Ennio Morricone",
        optionD: "Howard Shore",
        optionE: "Ramin Djawadi",
        correctAnswer: "Ramin Djawadi"
    },
    {                   
        question: "In the GoT saga &quotKhaleesi&quot means: ",
        optionA: "Mother of Dragons",
        optionB: "Queen",
        optionC: "Khal's Spouse",
        optionD: "Breaker of Chains",
        optionE: "Moon of my Life",
        correctAnswer: "Khal's Spouse"
    },
    {                   
        question: "How tall is &quotThe Wall&quot: ",
        optionA: "700 Feet",
        optionB: "800 Feet",
        optionC: "900 Feet",
        optionD: "1000 Feet",
        optionE: "Nobody knows",
        correctAnswer: "700 Feet"
    },
    {                   
        question: "Which of Daenery's dragons are the largest: ",
        optionA: "Rhaegal",
        optionB: "Drogon",
        optionC: "Viserion",
        optionD: "Balerion",
        optionE: "They all have the same age",
        correctAnswer: "Drogon"
    }

]

const STATS = {
    questionIndex: 0,
    correct: 0,
    incorrect: 0
}